let questions = [
    {
        numb: 0,
        question: "Ready to take the quiz again?",
        answer: "YES, I AM READY!",
        options: [
            "YES, I AM READY!",
            "NO",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Schrödinger’s equation required the use of quantum numbers to describe each electron within an atom corresponding to the orbital size, shape, and orientation in space.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "If  l = 1, then the orbital is called a p-orbital with two lobes of high electron density on either side of the nucleus, for an hourglass or dumbbell shape.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "The spin quantum number (ms) indicates the direction the electron is spinning.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "The magnetic quantum number (ml) refers to the rotation or the spin on how electrons move on their own axis as they move around the nucleus.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "The p-orbital has more complex shapes.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "The smaller the value of n, the higher the energy, and the closer to the orbital is to the nucleus.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "The correct order of atomic orbitals is s-orbital, p-orbital, d-orbital, f-orbital.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "In the orbital box diagram, the f-subshell has 5 orbitals.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Hund's Rule requires that the electrons fill the orbitals in a sub level one by one, before pairing the electrons in orbitals spin in opposite directions.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "P-subshell holds a maximum of 10 electrons.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "The atomic number is equal to the number of electrons.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Electron configuration is the distribution of nucleus on the main energy level and sub-energy level.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "The Aufbau Principle requires that the electrons occupy the lowest possible energy level before filling up the next.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "A quantum number is a pictorial representation of electron configuration.",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "There are only two possible positive values for ms : +1/2 and -1/2.",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False" 
        ]
    },

    ]